RAKSHIT SAINI

Flutter Developer

My Contact

rkshtsaini@gmail.com

+919166585813

Narnaul, Haryana

Hard Skill

- Dart/Flutter framework
- RESTful APIs
- State Management Getx, Provider
- FireBase
- UI/UX- Figma, Adobe XD

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- Global Institute of Technology, Jaipur Bachelor of Engineering - IT Completed in 2020
- Zinc Vidyalaya, Hurda, Bhilwara Higher Secondary Completed in 2016
- Zinc Vidyalaya, Hurda, Bhilwara Senior Secondary
 Completed in 2014

About Me

Am a skilled Mobile Developer who has around I years of experience with Android Mobile App development and Flutter Hybrid Mobile App development. As a developer, take great pride in making sure all of projects are up to client's satisfaction, all deadlines are met and quality assurance is carefully considered. Place customer satisfaction above all, and will bend over backwards to ensure customer satisfaction. In addition, promise to always deliver honest and speedy services.

Professional Experience

JPLoft Solution Pvt. Ltd May 2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Powerful skills in API Integration.
- Design and Build sophisticated and highly scalable apps using Flutter
- Explore feasible architectures for implementing new features.
- Follow the best practices while developing the app and also keeping everything structured and well documented.

PurgeSoft

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Explored about basic understanding of Agile development and why it is necessary.
- Maintaining the quality of code using architectural pattern.

BYJU'S - Business Developmet Trainee Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

Key Skills:

• Improved Communication Skills.

Zeetron Network Pvt. Ltd Jun 2019 – Aug 2019

• Internship in Android-Java

Achievements

2013 - 2015 Districs Level - Basketball

2015 State Level Cbse North Zone -

Badminton